addintools.com 2017-05-22

# Addintools Privacy Policy

##  Addintools.com Privacy Policy

###  General statement

AddinTools fully respects your right to privacy, and will not collect any personal information about you without your clear permission. Any personal information which you volunteer to AddinTools will be treated with the appropriate standards of security and confidentiality.

###  Collection and use of personal information

AddinTools does not collect any personal data about you on this website or in connection with any other service, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us, by purchasing a product from us, by downloading a product from us, or by registering your product with us, or by using our online feedback form). When you purchase a product from AddinTools, we don't collect any credit card or other payment details. Please note that credit card information may be retained by our billing provider(PayPal, MyCommerce or BlueSnap) as a record of any transaction we undertake with you.

If AddinTools has your email address, we may contact you by email to advise you of product updates, subscribe you to our newsletter or offer you AddinTools or third party products. You can opt out from receiving these emails at any time. AddinTools may also contact you in relation to customer support queries which you lodge. 

###  Collection and use of technical information

AddinTools will make no attempt to identify individual visitors. The technical information will be used only by AddinTools, and only for statistical and other administrative purposes.
